workday.com 2019-06-08

# Workday Privacy Policy

Data privacy is important to the Workday Group (Workday), which includes Workday, Inc. and its affiliates. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you as a visitor to workday.com or other Workday websites that link to this Privacy Statement, how Workday will use the information provided, and with whom we may share the information. The Statement describes your choices and rights related to the information that is provided to or collected by Workday.  

**The Workday Service**  
As part of the Workday Service, customers may load data into the Service. Workday will not share or distribute any such Customer Data except as provided in the contractual agreement between Workday and the customer, or as may be required by law. Please refer to the Workday Service Privacy Policy for more details.  

If you are a user of the Workday Service, your use of Workday is governed by your organization’s policies. Please direct your privacy questions or concerns to your employer or your organization’s Workday administrators.  

### How Workday Collects and Uses Information

**Information Collection**  
You may choose to provide us with your personal information, such as your name, email address, company information, street address, and telephone number in order to obtain information about our services. For example you may request information via a form, ask for support via “Contact Sales” forms or similar features, register or attend events or webinars, access or download certain content or participate in other interactions with us.

In order to access some areas of Workday, including Workday Community, you will need to have an account with a username and password. As part of your account, you may choose to provide us with additional information, such as a photo, social media profiles, or areas of expertise.

If you register to attend a Workday-sponsored event, we will require certain information including your name, email address, company, and in some instances, emergency contact. When registering for any event, we may also require you to provide billing information (such as billing name and address, and credit card number).

Workday or Workday Service providers may use website tracking technologies to observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as an IP address) relating to your use of our websites and services. We may also use log files, cookies, and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click, and other actions you take when accessing our websites, services, or emails.

When you choose to use a Workday mobile app we will collect information from your device, such as your photos, contacts, or precise geolocation data, to enable some functions in accordance with your device settings. For more information about our mobile app, please see the section below on **Mobile Applications**.

**Use**  
This section describes some of the ways in which Workday uses the information we collect. Please note that there may be other uses, which we would describe to you when we collect the information.

Workday uses the information we collect about you to provide you with Workday websites, services, and support. For example, if you provide information to us in a “Contact Us” form, we will use your information to respond to the request and communicate with you.

Workday uses your information for event planning and management, including registration, billing, and ways to connect with other event attendees, or to contact you further about relevant products and services. Any information you provide about emergency contacts or dietary preferences would be used for your safety and health purposes.

We may use the contact information we collect from you and information about your activity on our websites to send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as product announcements, newsletters, educational materials, details on upcoming events and other marking communications. We also use it to send administrative information, such as notices related to products, services, or policy changes.  

We use the information we collect to understand how our websites and services are being used and to make improvements. For example, we may use the search queries entered into Workday Community to improve search capabilities or performance. As another example, we may use questions posted or comments on Workday Community to enrich the content or help guide future enhancements to our products and services.  

Your information also may be used to personalize your experience on our websites. Workday or our services providers use website tracking technologies to display products or features that are tailored to your interests and to present advertising on other sites. For more information on these technologies see the section “Tracking Technologies and Targeted Advertising.” For more information on managing your choices in relation to cookies, click **Cookie Preferences** in the footer.  

We may use your information to diagnose website technical problems, as well as to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate potential security issues, as well as fraudulent or illegal activity.

In some instances, we may combine the information you have provided to us with other publicly available information. We may also purchase data from third parties and combine this with information we have already collected. We use this combined information to update, expand, and analyze our marketing leads; identify new customers; and create more tailored advertising.

If you participate in a Workday-offered education or training course, your enrollment and attendance information will be recorded to track and potentially report your participation and completion. For example, completion of Workday certifications by a services partner may be visible to Workday and our customers, and completion of a training course may also be visible to the entity making the training available to you. This registration and tracking may be conducted by third parties on behalf of Workday.

**Disclosure**  
Workday may share information with Workday affiliates, and third-party service providers or vendors contracted to provide services on our behalf. These third-party service providers or vendors may use information we provide to them only as instructed by Workday.

Workday may offer the following solely or jointly with third parties or partners: webinars, events, whitepaper downloads, or other services related to Workday offerings or services. We may share your contact information and interests in these offerings or services with these approved third parties to communicate with you about Workday.

When you attend an event (either sponsored by Workday or one where Workday is a participating vendor) and have your badge scanned, your information will be shared with Workday, as well as with any partner or third party participating in that event, and potentially with the entity sponsoring your attendance at the event. For example, if your badge is scanned as you attend a session at a Workday-sponsored conference, Workday and any co-presenters will have access to that information to understand who was in attendance, and potentially follow up with you on relevant products or services. If you do not want your information shared with Workday or partners in this manner, do not have your badge scanned. If your badged is scanned by a partner or a third party at an event, your information will be governed by that party’s privacy statement.

Workday may disclose information if we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal processes; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the website Terms and Conditions; and/or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

If Workday goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information may be among the assets transferred.

**Workday Forums**  
You may post comments or questions on our websites; for example, on a blog, community site, or developer forum. Some of these forums allow you to provide your personal information and create a profile. Personal information you submit in these public areas can be read and collected by others who access them. You should only post personal information to online forums with the awareness that the information will be available to others in the forum (unless stated otherwise). Comments posted by individuals in an online forum reflect their own views and should not be considered to reflect the opinion of Workday.

### Tracking Technologies and Targeted Advertising

Workday or Workday service providers may observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as an IP address) relating to your use of Workday websites. We may collect and store this information and combine this information with other personal information provided to Workday.

Workday and our service providers use cookies and other similar technologies, such as web beacons, HTML5 Local Storage, local shared objects, tags, and scripts on our websites and in email communications. We use these technologies to authenticate your access to various areas of our websites, understand your interests, analyze web traffic, combat fraud, provide interest-based advertising, improve our products and services as further described above in the Use section, and tailor content to your preferences. In messages we send, we may use these technologies to track their effectiveness.  

You can configure your browser settings to manage certain tracking technology interactions. For some tracking technologies you may need to take additional steps to manage their use and removal. Some of these technologies may operate across all of your browsers.

Online advertising may use information collected about your web browsing behavior, such as the pages you have visited or the searches you have conducted. This information may be used to display more relevant advertisements and content to you on non-Workday websites. The information used for targeted advertising may come from Workday or through third-party ad networks.

If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising on our websites, please click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (if you are located in Switzerland, the United Kingdom or the European Union, please click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note, this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

For additional information about the cookies and the tracking technologies Workday uses on our sites, and to manage your preferences, please click “Cookie Preferences” in the footer of this page. Below please review how Workday uses different categories of cookies.  

Type of Cookie | Description  
---|---  
Required | These cookies and similar technologies enable basic features of the site to function and collect statistical information about visitors to our website to manage site usage. All of the information collected is aggregated and used anonymously. There are also some cookies that will enable a more personalized experience. But we will not use these cookies until you opt in to their functionality.  
Functional | Functional technologies allow the Workday website to remember information you have entered or choices you make, and provide enhanced and more personal features based on your interaction with the site.  
Advertising | Advertising technologies are used to deliver advertising that is relevant to your interests. These technologies are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement and to help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. After visiting our site, you may see an advertisement for Workday on another site.  
  
**Do Not Track**  
Without a common industry or legal standard for interpreting Do Not Track (DNT) signals, Workday does not respond to browser DNT signals. We will continue to monitor further development of a DNT standard by the privacy community and industry.

### Additional Workday Privacy Information

**The Workday Cloud Platform**  
The Workday Cloud Platform allows partners and developers to build applications independent of Workday. Before using these applications, please review the relevant privacy statement and terms of service.

**Mobile Applications    
**When you are using a Workday mobile application, Workday may obtain information from or access data stored on your device, to provide services related to the relevant mobile application. Workday uses this information to deliver requested application services, to continue to improve our mobile applications, and to facilitate event participation, such as providing event schedules and the opportunity to connect with event attendees. For example, when you are using a Workday mobile application, we may access your camera to allow you to upload photographs to the mobile service; access your calendar, social media, and contact information to allow you to interact with other event attendees; or access the geographic location of your device to enable you to identify nearby contacts. Workday may also collect information from your usage of the mobile application to improve events and services, communicate with you about the event and relevant products and services, and for security purposes.

You may configure Workday mobile applications, and this configuration will affect how information from your device is accessed and obtained in the mobile application.

The Workday mobile application uses third party services for enabling easier access to the application, troubleshooting and improvement, and in conjunction with some services mentioned above. These services, such as Google Analytics allow Workday to view aggregated information about end user usage and interactions. Where possible, Workday takes steps to minimize or mask the information sent to third parties (such as encoding the data). These services do not collect any Customer Data as described in the Service privacy statement.

**Security**  
Workday employs reasonable and appropriate physical and logical security measures to protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, and unintentional disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your password or other form of authentication involved in accessing password-protected or secured resources. In order to protect you and your information, Workday may suspend your use of a website without notice, pending an investigation, if any security breach is suspected.

**Data Retention**  
We will retain your personal information only as long as needed to provide you with services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Data entered into the Workday Service is retained in accordance with the agreement between the Workday Customer and Workday.

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on this website and links to the Privacy Statement will indicate that the statement has been changed or updated. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement for any changes. For new users, changes or updates are effective upon posting. For existing users, changes or updates are effective 30 days after posting.

### Global Privacy Considerations

Personal information collected by Workday may be stored and processed in the United States or in any other country where Workday or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or third-party service providers maintain facilities. When you provide personal information to Workday, you consent to the processing and transfer of your information within the United States and around the world. We follow applicable data protection laws when transferring personal information.

**European Privacy Rights**  
Workday will process your personal information for the legitimate interests of Workday, or, when needed, with your explicit consent. If you have provided consent for the processing of your personal information, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time, which will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent was withdrawn. You have the right to request access to and rectification or erasure of your personal information, as well as the right to restrict processing, object to processing, and under certain circumstances the right to data portability. You have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority if you believe that we have not complied with the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation with regard to your personal information.

**APEC Program Statement**  
Workday privacy practices, described in this Privacy Statement, comply with the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (“APEC”) Cross-Border Privacy Rules (“CBPR”) System. The APEC CBPR system provides a framework for organizations to ensure protection of personal information transferred among participating APEC economies. More information about the APEC framework can be found [here](http://www.apec.org/Groups/Committee-on-Trade-and-Investment/~/media/Files/Groups/ECSG/CBPR/CBPR-PoliciesRulesGuidelines.ashx).

**EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Statement**  
Workday complies with both the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom to the United States, and from Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Workday has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Statement and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome).

View our EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Notices.

### Contacting Workday

**Updating Your Choices**  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, or if at any time after providing your personal information to Workday you want to update, change, unsubscribe, or request removal or deletion of your information, or if you would like to assert any of the rights listed above, please direct your request to [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com?subject=Privacy%20Contact) or via postal mail at the contact information listed below. Workday will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

If you prefer not to receive marketing communications from us, you may do so by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our marketing emails or clicking “Email Subscriptions” in the footer of the Workday.com website. Please note that, as applicable, we will continue to send you necessary business communications after you have opted out, such as information about events, service announcements and other important communications.

**Workday Contact Information**  
You may reach our Privacy Team at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com?subject=Privacy%20Contact).

Alternatively you may reach us by addressing regular mail to the following addresses:

_Headquarters_  
Workday, Inc.  
Attn.: Privacy  
6110 Stoneridge Mall Road  
Pleasanton, CA 94588  
United States

_European Union_  
Workday Limited  
Attn.: Privacy  
Kings Building  
May Lane  
Dublin 7 Ireland

**Additional Questions or Concerns**  
If you have an unresolved EEA, UK or Swiss privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant EU data protection authority or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, as applicable. If you have a non-EEA and UK or non-Swiss privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

_Last Updated: April 11, 2019_
